(Bernadette:)Oh, I take pacts
very seriously.
(Bernadette:)One time at my lab,
a petri dish
(Bernadette:)of genetically modified
super-virus went missing.
(Bernadette:)That day we made a pinky swear
never to admit
(Bernadette:)we crossed Ebola
with the common cold.
(Howard:)Why the hell
(Howard:)would you cross Ebola
with the common cold?
(Bernadette:)We never did.
(Bernadette:)That would be
a terrible, terrible thing.
(Girl(arriving):)Hi. Sorry I'm late--
I was at the gym.
(Girl(arriving):)Spin class--
worked up quite a sweat.
(Bernadette:)Joy, this is Leonard.
Leonard, this is Joy.
(Sheldon:)Hi.
Hi.
(Joy:)You don't look
like a genius.
(Joy:)Go ahead, say
something smart.
(Sheldon:)Uh...
Aah! Time's up.
(Joy:)Just kidding.
(Joy:)First thing you need
to know about me:
(Joy:)I'm hilarious.
(Stuart:)Yeah.
(Leonard:)So, Bernadette tells me
(Leonard:)she knows you from
self-defense classes?
(Joy:)Yeah. Israeli Krav Maga.
(Joy:)Lots of fun.
(Joy:)Basically,
a hundred different ways
(Joy:)to rip a guy's nuts off.